{
    "subject": "resource/Vesta_M._Roy",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Dearborn,_Michigan",
    "human_readable": "Vesta M. Roy was born in Dearborn, Michigan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9375348687171936,
            "question": "Where was Vesta M. Roy born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8884952664375305,
            "question": "Where might Vesta M. Roy have lived besides Dearborn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8213339447975159,
            "question": "What year was Vesta M. Roy born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6759275794029236,
            "question": "Is Dearborn a city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6289452910423279,
            "question": "What state is Dearborn in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5309644937515259,
            "question": "Who are some famous people born in Dearborn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46270349621772766,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Vesta M. Roy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37907350063323975,
            "question": "Are there any other places called Dearborn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33358174562454224,
            "question": "What kind of work might Vesta M. Roy have done?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21575576066970825,
            "question": "What is Michigan known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Vesta M. Roy was born in Dearborn, Michigan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3280_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work might Vesta M. Roy have done?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3280_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other places called Dearborn?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3280_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Vesta M. Roy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3280_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3280_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3280_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3280_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3280_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3280_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3280_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3280_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3280_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3280_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3280_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Vesta M. Roy was born in Dearborn, Michigan, which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}